Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - Research Management Group., 1983-1986. (Box 645, Folder 3)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - AAU Clearinghouse on University-Industry Relations., 1985-1986. (Box 645, Folder 4-5)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - MICRO., 1981-1984. (Box 645, Folder 6-7)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - Research Management Group., 1982. (Box 645, Folder 8)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university., 1958-1981. (Box 645, Folder 9)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - Research Management Group., 1980-1981. (Box 645, Folder 10)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - AAB book on research., 1979-1981. (Box 645, Folder 11)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - Research Management Group., 1979-1980. (Box 646, Folder 1)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university., 1977-1979. (Box 646, Folder 2)
- Organized Research and Museums - role of the university - Research Management Group., 1979. (Box 646, Folder 3)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - policy on organized research units., 1971-1996. (Box 646, Folder 4)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - policy on organized research units - directories., 1995. (Box 646, Folder 5)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - policy on organized research units - policies., 1971-1995. (Box 646, Folder 6)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - policy on organized research units - directories., 1974-1993. (Box 646, Folder 7)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - policy on organized research units., 1973-1975. (Box 646, Folder 8)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - policy on organized research units Academic Senate Budget Council on ORUs., 1972-1973. (Box 646, Folder 9-10)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Energy Research Institute Group., 1993-1997. (Box 646, Folder 11)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general., 1989-1995. (Box 646, Folder 12)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Energy Research Institute Group., 1988-1992. (Box 646, Folder 13)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Center for Religion., 1990-1992. (Box 646, Folder 14)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general., 1984-1990. (Box 646, Folder 15)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Institute for Theoretical Studies., 1988-1989. (Box 646, Folder 16)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general., 1983-1987. (Box 646, Folder 17)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Nonlinear Science, Institute for., 1983-1987. (Box 646, Folder 18)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Center for International and Strategic Affairs., 1984-1986. (Box 646, Folder 19)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Alzheimer Disease Research Center., 1984-1985. (Box 647, Folder 1)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general., 1977-1984. (Box 647, Folder 2-3)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Appropriate Technology., 1977-1984. (Box 647, Folder 4)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Energy Research Institute Group., 1979-1982. (Box 647, Folder 5)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general - Institute of Advanced Study in the Arts., 1980-1982. (Box 647, Folder 6)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - general., 1972-1981. (Box 647, Folder 7)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - Institute for Fusion Studies., 1970-1980. (Box 647, Folder 8)
- Organized Research and Museums - general - Proposed Organized Research Units - EAR Institute - Institute for Communicative Disorders., 1971-1980. (Box 647, Folder 9)
- Organized Research and Museums - Institutes - Neuropsychiatric Institute - transfer of NPI., 1971-1975, 1985-1986 (Box 647, Folder 10-13)
- Campus Administration and Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's files - speeches (see also boxes 142 and 205)., 1979-1992. (Box 647, Folder 14)
- Instruction - accreditation (see also box 504, folder 4)., 1970-1972. (Box 647, Folder 15)
- Instruction - accreditation - Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC) - Parts 1 and 2., 1967-1973. (Box 647, Folder 16-17)